A Guide to the Bryan Family Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Union Seminary Magazine- Early Recollections of John Randolph, 1893 Sep-Oct; 1 item (Box Box 3)
- Article re: Frances Bland Randolph, Petersburg, Va., Daily Index-Appeal, 1901 Feb 24; 1 item (Box Box 3)
- John Randolph of Roanoke to Frances Bland Coalter, n.y. Sep 12; ALS (Box Box 3)
- John Randolph of Roanoke to Frances B. Tucker, ALS (Box Box 3)
- Lists of books in John Randolph of Roanoke's hand, 2 items (Box Box 3)
- John Randolph of Roanoke to John Coalter, ALS (Box Box 3)
- John Randolph of Roanoke: miscellaneous items, 3 items (Box Box 3)
- John Randolph of Roanoke - envelope to John Randolph Bryan and J. M. F. Bryan, 1 item (Box Box 3)
- Unidentified John Randolph of Roanoke manuscript, AL (Box Box 3)
- Nathaniel Beverley Tucker to Elizabeth Tucker Coalter Bryan, n.d.; 7 ALS (Box Box 3)
- "Anecdotes of John Randolph of Roanoke ", unidentifiable papers & 1 newspaper clipping, 3 items (Box Box 3)
- Statement by [Beverley Tucker] of conversation with Andrew Jackson concerning John Randolph of Roanoke; statement concerning visit of John Randolph of Roanoke with Jackson, [1833 Feb 21]; 2 AL (Box Box 3)
- Judith Randolph to John Randolph of Roanoke, 11 ALS (Box Box 3)
- [Elizabeth Tucker Coalter Bryan?] statement on will of John Randolph of Roanoke, 1 item (Box Box 3)
- 4 prints, John Randolph of Roanoke, Prints (Box Box 3)
- 3 prints, Confederate prints, n.d.; Prints (Box Box 3)
- John Randolph of Roanoke Prayer Book (1818) and Emmanuel Church Roll Book (1918), 1815; 1918; 2 items (Box Box 3)